BLAINE MILLER

bmiller@cenode.com ◆ 661.616.8654

SUMMARY

Industry-certified professional with six years in advanced technologies improving web-user experiences by definitive expertise in conceiving and implementing internet solutions that elevate brand image, generate revenues, and provide the basis for cost-effective content management and expansion. Acknowledged throughout career as a service-centric and process-driven leader and trouble-shooter while composing clean code and concise documentation that fully de-tails software development life cycles from development environment to production. Expertise in capitalizing on the advantages of web and streaming media technologies, creating usable and sale-able products, steering projects at mi- cro and macro levels, and delivering to specification, on time and on budget.

SKILLS

Website Development	SEO	Business Leadership
Web Analytics	PHP, MySQL, C#, Obj-c	Linux, Windows & Mac OS X
Web Architecture	Adobe Photoshop, Wordpress	Analysis of Web and Systems Security
Mobile App Development	Microsoft Office Suite	Develop and Maintain Customer Relationships

EXPERIENCE

Cenode 06/2013 - Present

Co Owner

Computer Repairs, Website Programming, Mobile Application Development, Design Assistant, Multimedia Director, Sales Agent, Customer Service, Web Architect, Security Analyst, Team Work Environment, Business Advisor RLS Industries 12/2012 - 08/2015

Website Manager

Migration of Wordpress Website, Website Design, Content Management, Web Architecture, Security Specialist, Independent Work Environment, Technical Advisor

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

DeVry University 2013 - 2015

Bachelors of Science, Computer Information Systems/Website Development

- Campus Involvement: Website Development Group
- Curriculum Highlights: Logic and Design; Architecture and Operating Systemsw/Lab; Connectivity w/Lab; Structured Analysis and Design; Introduction to Database w/Lab; Object-Oriented Analysis and Design; Computer Applications for Businessw/Lab; Project Management; Principles of InformationSystems Security; Programming w/Lab; Object-Oriented Programming w/Lab; Business Application Programming w/Lab; Web Interface Design w/Lab; Web Application Development w/Lab; Web Security; Principles of E-Commerce; Web Architecture w/Lab; Advanced Web Application Developmentw/Lab
- 3.83 GPA

Network+ 2009 Security+ 2011 A+ 2009 Mind Leaders